[Rel] Man, this honey bun is $2.75?! In THIS economy? Yo, I'm writing my congressman.
[Jace] You ain't writing nobody. Pick your snack and let's go.
[Rel] Aight, aight — but real talk though. Some dude named Dre been asking 'bout you. West side type. Clean but... off.
[Jace] I don't know no Dre.
[Nia] Heaven knows... I've been waiting on this... mmhmm...
[Nia] Oh my God. Oh my GOD.
[Nia] Kingdom Records, Jace. They actually listened. They want to meet me next week.
[Jace] I told you. I been told you. Wasn't nobody gonna sleep on that voice.
[Nia] You good? You got that look again.
[Jace] I'm good. Just handling business.
[Dre] Tell your cousin Marcus made a deal with the feds. His name's in it. He's got seventy-two hours to decide what he wants to do about that.
[Rel] ...
[Dre] Have a good night, little cousin.
[Rel] Jace... pick up. Jace, pick up the phone, bro. It's about Marcus.
[Uncle] Jace. Sit down, nephew.
[Jace] I'm standing.
[Uncle] Then you already know.